**** FLOW ****

- header: The header will be shown on all pages. Show login/signup (or logout) button, site title and maybe a hamburger menu for more options?

- home screen: show an option for random quizzes (selected by category and level), and a list of quizzes. **considerations: when the db has a ton of quizzes, you can't show them all on the homepage so you'll have to show just a handful. Maybe you can show the 10 newest by category? Or 10 random? Or???

- quiz-view: When user starts quiz, load quiz view




******* RATINGS *******

- user sees current rating when no mouseover
- when user hovers over stars, all stars turn grey by default but turn yellow up to the point that the user is hovering
- user clicks to vote
- user gets dialog confirming vote with OK or cancel
	- if cancel, nothing happens
	- if OK, vote is registered
- rating goes back to showing the quiz's rating and hovering doesn't do anything anymore
- user cannot vote more than once





	******* FEATURES TO ADD *********
	
	Total time spent online
	Avg time per quiz by level and total
	Time spent on each individual quiz
	Number of times each quiz has been taken
	List of quizzes you have authored
	Ratings for your authored quizzes
	Ability to reset all your stats to zero
	Badges for:
		Completed 1, 10, 25, 50, 100, 200, etc. quizzes
		Created 1, 5, 10, etc. quizzes




****** THE QUESTIONS ******


Level 1 - Make the questions as easy as you can without actually giving away the answer
	- time, months, colors, shapes, very basic vocabulary, very basic grammar, etc., everything should be present, past or future tense. Basic conversation such as greetings, etc.
	
Level 2 - A bit harder than Level 1 but not much. Add past tense and future 




Level 5 - A native speaker would find it difficult to get 100%






----------------------------------------------------------

dbh.php file contents in case you need it:

<?php

// connect to live site databse
//$conn = mysqli_connect('hostname', 'username', 'password', 'databasename');

// connect to localhost database for development
$conn = mysqli_connect('localhost', 'root', '', 'quizzer');


// only use mysqli_connect_error() for testing!
if (!$conn) {
	die("Connection failed: ".mysqli_connect_error());
}

----------------------------------------------------------







Just in case you ever need this again...

var quizzes = [{
	creator: "Syl",
	language: "English",
	level: 1,
	category: "geography",
	topic: "",
	randomProblems: true,
	randomAnswers: true,
	problems: [{
		question: "What is the national anthem of Canada?",
		answerChoices: ["Woah Canada!", "Hey Canada!", "Oh Canada!", "O Canada!"],
		correctAns: 3,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "In which country can you find the Grand Canyon?",
		answerChoices: ["Germany", "United States of America", "Canada", "Alaska"],
		correctAns: 1,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "On which continent is Libya?",
		answerChoices: ["North America", "Australia", "Europe", "Africa"],
		correctAns: 3,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "Kuala Lumpur is in which country?",
		answerChoices: ["Malaysia", "Thailand", "Indonesia", "Philippines"],
		correctAns: 0,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "Which city in Japan is famous for its okonomiyaki?",
		answerChoices: ["Tokyo", "Nagoya", "Osaka", "Fukuoka"],
		correctAns: 2,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }]
}, {
	creator: "Syl",
	language: "English",
	level: 2,
	category: "vocabulary",
	topic: "",
	randomProblems: true,
	randomAnswers: true,
	problems: [{
		question: "What is the best synonym for 'happy'?",
		answerChoices: ["Ambivalent", "Jealous", "Glad", "Smiling"],
		correctAns: 2,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "What is the synonym of 'cold'?",
		answerChoices: ["Wide", "Frigid", "Deserted", "Friendly"],
		correctAns: 1,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "Choose the most appropriate group of synonyms for 'very good'.",
		answerChoices: ["Amazing, incredible, surprising, excellent", "Incredible, awesome, sick, off the hook", "Excellent, dependable, amazing, superb", "Awesome, repulsive, superlative, off the hook"],
		correctAns: 1,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }]
}, {
	creator: "Syl",
	language: "English",
	level: 2,
	category: "vocabulary",
	topic: "",
	randomProblems: true,
	randomAnswers: true,
	problems: [{
		question: "What is the best antonym for 'happy'?",
		answerChoices: ["Ambivalent", "Jealous", "Glad", "Angry"],
		correctAns: 3,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "What is the antonym of 'cold'?",
		answerChoices: ["Hot", "Frigid", "Deserted", "Friendly"],
		correctAns: 0,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }, {
		question: "What's the antonym of 'sad'",
		answerChoices: ["Happy", "Excited", "Depressed", "Anxious"],
		correctAns: 0,
		notes: "",
		flagged: false,
		flagCode: "",
		picLoc: "",
		audLoc: "",
		vidLoc: ""
  }]
}];
